misssamoapageant.ws 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy for Bravenet.com

### PRIVACY POLICY TERMS

Our site uses cookies to facilitate use of the members area and some services. They are also used to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and to deliver content specific to your interests. 

Information may be shared with partners that provide co-branded services but this information is limited to that required to implement such services, and will only occur with the member's consent to participate in such services. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or country). We use customer contact information (email address) from the registration form to send the user information about improvements, new features, or important changes in Bravenet's services.

The Bravenet site contains links to other sites. Bravenet is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such Web sites. When visiting such sites, we urge you to be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Public Services**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, classified ads, and guestbooks available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Children's Privacy**

Our service is not available to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include secure servers, encrypted passwords, and other security measures to guarantee the privacy of our members. We do not store credit card information on any Bravenet servers. 

**Mailing Lists**

a) Members Update, Tips and Tricks, Freebies and Special Offers mailing lists:
    When registering a Bravenet account, you may agree to subscribe to our Members Update, Tips and Tricks, Resources, Freebies or Special Offers mailing lists. These lists may contain third-party sponsorships. You may unsubscribe from these mailing lists at any time by removing your email address here: [ Unsubscribe](http://www.bravenet.com/unsub.php). 

You have the following options for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications or to terminate your Bravenet account. 

  1. All mailing lists have unsubscribe instructions contained at the bottom of the emails. 
  2. You can go to the Support Center to contact Bravenet support. 
  3. You can login to the Members Area here and delete your account. 
  4. You can login to the Members Area here to change any information previously provided. 

b) Mailing List Service
    When you register to use our Mailing List Services, you must abide by all applicable legislation relating to the proper collection and use of email addresses. We will neither use, nor disclose the email addresses or personal information of your subscribers to any third party unless we are compelled by law or, in our sole discretion, whenever we believe an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying or providing such information to the appropriate authorities.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us in the [Support Center](http://support.bravenet.com/). 

return to top »
